CONTACT

PHONE:

226-961-4042

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/manish-jain-733132188/

EMAIL:

manish.jain5725@gmail.com

PROFILE

An innovative programmer with almost a year of experience as an application developer; with a positive attitude, extremely focused with an ability to multitask, excellent leadership skills, an amazing team player with a great task and time managing skills, and a track record of consistently exceeding expectations.

SKILLS

Programming Languages

C/C++

Python

Java

JavaScript

TypeScript

Backend

Node JS

SpringSecurity

SpringBoot

Thymeleaf

Frontend

Angular

BootStrap

React

HTML

• jQuery

CSS

Database

MySQL

MongoDB

Others

• Gif

Microsoft Word

Maven • Microsoft Excel

AWARDS

- 2nd prize for my research paper on Electromagnetism.
- 3rd position in West Zone New Delhi in painting competition
- Best Artist award in school for year 2006 and 2008
- Winner of football cup in school.

MANISH JAIN

Full Stack Engineer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Aureus Infosys, Application Developer Aug 2019–Present

- Design Web application for Loblaws.
- Delivered screens naming Dispatch and Route Change.
- Communicated closely with clients about business requirements and delivered the desired product.
- Successfully worked in a team to deliver the project in time.
- Used New Tools for the development of the project.

City of Windsor, Arena Attendant

Jan 2019-May 2019

Walmart, Cashier

Sep 2018–Dec 2018

PROJECTS

- Meeting Planner using Java
- Aureus Infosys Website using JavaScript, HTML5, PHP, BootStrap and CSS (https://aureusinfosys.com/)
- Color Selection Game using JavaScript, HTML5 and CSS
- Interactive Key Press using Howler JS, Paper JS, JavaScript, HTML5 and CSS
- To-Do List using HTML5 and CSS

EDUCATION

University of Windsor Masters of Engineering May 2018 – Apr 2019 Electrical and Computer

Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University Aug 2013 – June 2017

Bachelor of Technology Electronics and Communication